Mike North: 所以我们可以使用索引签名
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So
we can use index signatures
与其他类型结合在一起。
in combination with other types.
这就是我在这里展示的一些东西。
And this is where I'm actually
showing off a couple things here.
第一，我创造了另一个
Number one, I have created another
和我们刚才用的是同一个名字，对吗？
interface with the same name of
what we were just using, right?
在这里，我们有 PhoneNumberDict。
Up here, we had PhoneNumberDict.
迈克 · 诺斯: 现在在这里，同样的名字。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: And
now down here, same exact name.
如果我们看这个，如果我试图移除它，我们现在得到一个错误。
And if we look at this, if I try to
remove it, we're now getting an error.
让我们看看下面
So let's look below and
研究我们添加的内容，找出为什么有些东西会出错。
study what we've added in order to figure
out why something might be erroring.
我添加的是新类型。
What I've added is new types.
他们说我们有了新的必需品。
They kind of say we have
new required properties.
每个人必须有一个家庭电话号码和一个办公室电话号码。
Everyone must have a home phone number,
and an office phone number.
而且，索引签名仍然存在于所有这一切之下。
And, the index signature still
exists underneath all of that.
这就是为什么如果我们试图删除这里,
So that's what's making it so
if we attempt to delete this up here,
我们发现了一个家不见了的问题。
we're getting an issue
where home is missing.
现在我们完全可以在这里安全地添加另一个,
Now we could totally add
another one here safely,
迈克 · 诺斯: iPhone,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: iPhone,
我只需要一个逗号。
I just need a comma.
这很好，我们可以根据自己的需要自由添加或删除这些内容。
And that's fine and we're free to add and
remove this as we see fit.
因此，您可以将索引签名与
So you can use index
signatures in combination with
关于对象类型的其他知识。
anything else that we have
learned about object types.
Mike North: 通常这是一个后备方案，你可以指定某些事情
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Often this will be a
fallback where you specify certain things
比如，我们知道我们可以访问这些东西。
like, we know we can access these things.
所以，举个例子来说，这个东西被交到手上是很方便的。
So, for example, it would be
convenient to be handed this thing.
我不需要检查家和办公室是否没有定义。
I don't have to check whether home and
the office are undefined.
如果你知道他们出现在
If you know they're present for
当然，有这么一个可以用的东西要好得多。
sure, it's much nicer to be handed
this thing that's ready to go.
但是，那里可能有可选的额外的东西
But, there may be optional
extra stuff there and
索引签名是一种方便输入的方法。
an index signature would be
a way to facilitate typing that.
迈克 · 诺斯: 我们已经演示过了，但是
&gt;&gt; Mike North: We kind of
demonstrated this already, but
家肯定在那儿，办公室肯定在那儿。
home is definitely there,
office is definitely there.
由于索引签名，移动设备将不得不未定义。
Mobile will have to be undefined
due to the index signature.
这里我们看到的是声明合并。
So what we're seeing here
is declaration merging.
Mike North: 我们发现我们可以把索引堆叠在其他东西之上。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: And we're seeing that we
can stack indexes on top of other things.
关于接口，我想指出的最后一点是
The last thing I wanna point out
about interfaces loops back to
我们之前讨论的化名类型。
the type alias discussion
we were having earlier.
接口有点像函数，它们像函数一样被解析。
Interfaces are kind of like functions,
they're parsed like functions.
在这里，我们知道一个接口的存在
In that,
we know that an interface exists and
有一个特定的名称，因为我们经过解析的东西。
has a particular name as we
go through in parse things.
但是，只有当我们尝试真正访问它的时候
But, only when we attempt
to actually access it and
使用它将我们最终找出什么是允许的类型为这件事情。
use it will we end up figuring out what
are the allowable types for this thing.
所以，类型别名是急切排序,
So, type aliases are kind
of sorted out eagerly,
接口是懒洋洋地整理出来的。
interfaces are sorted out lazily.
如果我们来看第一个例子,
So if we were to go up here to our
first example, and we were to say,
我们要想办法让这种类型的东西运作起来。
we were to try to figure out
a way to make this type work.
如果我们只是说，接口数组和
If we were just gonna say,
interface number array and
我要在这里作弊一点，迈克 · 诺斯: 延伸。
I'm gonna cheat a little bit here,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Extends.
和 numVals 数组，分号,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: And
array of numVals, semicolon,
现在这个起作用了，为什么？
now this ends up working, why?
因为这有点像，就像一个函数，这样悬挂起来
Because this is kind of like,
just like a function that's hoisted so
我们可以在它使用之前或者定义之前引用它。
we can refer to it before it's used or
before it's defined.
数字，当我们通过和
Numval, by the time we go through and
解决这个问题，这实际上是快乐，它现在是一个界面。
sort this out, this is actually happy,
it's an interface now.
直到我们来到这里
Until we get down here and
解决这些问题，我们不一定知道这个接口能容纳什么。
sort out all of this, we don't necessarily
know what this interface can hold.
但是至少我们可以引用它，并且把它作为定义的一部分
But at least we can refer to it and
use it as part of the definition for
类型化名。
the type alias.
所以你可以创建一些等级类型的东西,
So you can create things that
are sort of hierarchical types,
自尊型。
self-reverential types.
有些人称之为递归类型，但是
Some people call this recursive types, but
你可以通过组合类型和接口来创建这样的东西。
you can create things like this through
combining types and interfaces.
迈克 · 诺斯: 让我们确认一下我没有撒谎。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Let's
make sure I'm not lying.
麦克 · 诺斯: 看起来不错，我们试试这个。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Looks good, let's try this.
迈克 · 诺斯: 看起来不错。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Looks good.
迈克 · 诺斯: 四个让它不开心。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Four makes it unhappy.
所以它可以保存嵌套的数组,
So it can hold our nested arrays,
它可以保存我们感兴趣的简单值，一切看起来都非常好。
it can hold the simple values we're
interested in, everything looks copacetic.
迈克 · 诺斯: 那么,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So that's,
希望你现在能明白这两者的区别。
hopefully now you understand
the difference between these two.
类型别名是渴望的，接口是懒惰的。
Type aliases are eager,
interfaces are lazy.
类型别名是非常灵活的，它们可以给任何类型命名,
Type aliases are extremely flexible, they
literally can give a name to any type,
任何用作变量类型的东西都适用于类型别名。
anything you would use as the type
of variable fits in a type alias.
接口或者你想用来做什么
Interfaces or what you would wanna use for
包含函数和数组的对象。
things that are objects which includes
functions and includes arrays.
当我说的东西是子类型的对象，我的意思是在 JavaScript 的意义。
when I say things that are sub-types of
object I mean in the JavaScript sense.
事物是不可改变的，对吗？
Things that are immutable things, right?
除了原语字符串，数字,
Everything except the primitive
like string, number,
恶霸，象征和未定义的
bully, and symbol and the undefined